CONTACT



+44 7975 697134



jackdomleo7@hotmail.com



https://jackdomleo.dev



28 Melksham Road, Nottingham, UK NG5 5RX

SKILLS

- → Basic knowledge of Adobe Creative Cloud software including Photoshop, Illustrator and Acrobat
- → Confident in identifying issues and acting on improving organic SEO
- → Competent in working in an agile environment to collaborate, develop and test ideas, bugs and new features
- → Confident in using and developing web applications using different programming languages, frameworks and IDE's. I have experience with:
 - HTML5, Twig HTML, Bootstrap 4 and Grav CMS
 - CSS3 and Sass/SCSS
 - JavaScript, jQuery,
 Vue.js and TypeScript
 - o Python
 - Git, Command Line and Markdown
 - IDE's such as JetBrains, Visual Studio and VS Code
 - Project management systems such as DevOps and Flow
 - o Mailchimp

Jack Domleo

Web/Software Developer

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am an energetic and enthusiastic person with experience working in a small IT team and a larger development team with experience working in an agile and waterfall environment. My present career aim is to progress in web/software development developing programs as a team and individually using services such as Microsoft Azure and Google Cloud. I enjoy a challenge and will tackle anything thrown at me. I enjoy the environment of working in IT and I find the development work interesting and satisfying. The opportunity to learn new skills and work with new technologies is particularly attractive to me.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mitrefinch, Nottingham (& York)

Developer

May 2019 - Present

As a Developer in this software company, my responsibilities include:

- Taking the lead on the stylesheets of the redesign of Mitrefinch's products using SCSS to make the styles as simple but effective as possible.
- Learning the C# programming language
- Working in a squad on a brand new product, primarily focusing on frontend development

Junior Developer

March 2019 - May 2019

As a Junior Developer in this software company, my responsibilities include:

- Taking the lead on the stylesheets of the redesign of Mitrefinch's products using SCSS to make the styles as simple but effective as possible.
- Learning the C# programming language
- Learning to work in an agile environment

I learned new skills every day and was eager to learn more.

flybmi, East Midlands Airport

IT Developer Apprentice

Sept 2018 - Feb 2019

As an IT Developer Apprentice for this airline, my responsibilities included:

- Worked towards BCS Level 3 in Software Development
- Developed new programs from a design specification using frameworks such as Bootstrap 4, Grav CMS, Core UI and Electron JS
- Created new templates using Twig HTML that can be accessed via the Grav CMS and maintaining the content on the flybmi.com website

During my time at flybmi, I gained 6 months' worth of knowledge and experience working in the airline industry and working together with other employees to develop an end product.

REFERENCES



Jon Mennell Delivery Team Lead Mitrefinch jon.mennell@mitrefinch.co.uk



Claire Abbot
Delivery Manager
Mitrefinch
+44 7519 107108
claire.abbott@mitrefinch.co.uk



George Smith Digital Systems Manager flybmi +44 7415 371200

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

- → Walking
- → Travelling & Days Out
- → Nottingham Panthers Ice Hockey games

ACHIEVEMENTS

- → Young Enterprise
 - Appointed as Managing and Finance Director for our team
- → Air Cadet Organisation
 - Completed NNAS, basic first aid and radio communication courses
- → Bronze & Silver DofE
 - Required teamwork, communication and survival skills
- → Black Belt
 - Achieved Black Belt in Karate, which took dedication
- \rightarrow Ice Hockey & Ice Skating
 - Completed up to UK Skate level 5 in ice skating and level 6 in ice hockey

Primark, Nottingham

Retail Assistant

June 2017 – Aug 2018

As a Retail Assistant for this high street clothing company, my responsibilities included:

- Answering customer queries and maintaining quality customer service
- Ensuring items are restocked and displayed effectively
- Training new starters with their duties (till training, department training)

During my time at Primark, I gained skills and experience in teamwork, customer service/engagement and merchandising.

EDUCATION

The Redhill Academy Sixth Form, Nottingham	2016-2018
A-level Computer Science	В
A-level Mathematics	В
A-level Physics	D
AS Chemistry	В

The Redhill Academy, Nottingham

2013-2016

GCSE Mathematics	A*
GCSE Physics	A*
GCSE German	A
GCSE Biology	A
GCSE Computer Science	В
GCSE Chemistry	В
GCSE Business Studies	В
GCSE English Language	В
GCSE English Literature	С
GCSE Further Mathematics	С

QUALIFICATIONS

- > Google Digital Garage Fundamentals of Digital Marketing
- ➤ BCS Level 2 ECDL in IT Application Distinction*

DRIVING LICENSE

Holder of a clean UK manual & automatic driving license since 22^{nd} Nov 2017.